(Howard:)Then our problem would be solved.
(Leonard:)Hang on, are we talking about
murdering Dennis Kim?
(Leonard:)I'm not saying no.
(Howard:)We don't have to go that far.
There are other means.
(Raj:)We can't send him back to North Korea.
(Raj:)He knows how to get out.
(Howard:)The only thing we need to do
is make this Kim kid lose his focus.
It won't happen. He is not interested
in anything but physics.
- What about biology?
- What?
(Howard:)You know, biology.
(Howard:)The one thing that can completely derail
a world-class mind.
- Howard, he's 15.
- Yeah, so?
When I was 15, I met Denise Palmeri...
(Howard:)...and my grade point average
fell from a 5.0 to a 1.8.
(Raj:)She was sleeping with you?
(Howard:)No, I just wasted a lot of time thinking
about what it would be like if she did.
(Sheldon(entering):)Oh, good, you're all here.
(Sheldon(entering):)I've decided that if the three of you drop
whatever you're working on and join me...
(Sheldon(entering):)...we could lick cold fusion
in less than a decade, 12 years tops.